<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Org-hub</string>
    <string-array name="arr">
        <item>RED</item>
        <item>BLUE</item>
        <item>GREEN</item>
        <item>PINK</item>
        <item>YELLOW</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="old"> A gray old woman sits all alone \n
Unloved uncherished and unknown \n
Sitting beside her broken door \n
Dreaming of days past long ago \n
When children played about her knee \n
Filling the air with childish glee \n
Tended by her with loving care \n
Knowing the blessing of a Mother prayer \n
But now they have gone each to his life \n
A girl to her husband a boy to his wife \n
Forgetful are they of her who sits here \n
Silently wiping a tricking tear \n
For striving for things in a life so brief \n
Blind their poor eyes to a dear Mother grief \n
But does she upbraid them in word or in mind \n
Nor does their neglect to her seem unkind \n
She will forgive and forget all unkindness they have shown \n
This poor old mother who sits alone \n

</string>

    <string name="oldq"> Make them count their age by FRIENDS not years, by SMILE not tears \! </string>

    <string name="ngo">
        Go spread to the needy,
        sweet charity bread\n
        For giving is living ,
        the angel said \n
        Oh must I be giving again and again ,
        My peevish and willful answer ran \n
        Oh no said the angel ,
        piercing me through \n
        Just give till the Lord ,
        stops giving to you\n
    </string>

    <string name="ngoq"> Because charity is a way to nation\'s prosperity</string>

    <string name="orphan">
        When I wake up in the morning
I look around and something’s just not there\n
No mommy … No daddy to wake me up
It really isn’t fair\n\n
        I have 60 friends to share my time
And there are my carers too\n
Sometimes we get volunteers
For excursions at the zoo\n\n

My clothes are all packed away
Inside my slide-out draw\n
My shoes are stacked up in a row
With 59 others … at the door\n\n

I have food in my belly
Bath twice a day … it’s really not so bad\n
But what I’d give for a bedside story
Read to me by Mum or dad\n\n

        What did I do that is so wrong?
What have I done so bad?\n
That I should have to live my life
Without both mum and dad\n

I have lived here since I was one
That was five years ago\n
Sometimes life just flashes by
But some days it goes real slow\n

I wake up often in my sleep
I’m afraid to lose my toys\n
When I turn seven … Is time to move
To live with 175 older boys\n


For 10 more years I need to wait
Until the day that I’m set free\n
When I can finally leave this orphanage
And rely just on me\n

I promise that when I have children
I will be there … To take care\n
To tuck them in to bed at night
And let them know I’m there\n

If you can share some of your wealth
For a better future is my goal\n
Knowing your money is helping orphans
Will be like feeding your own soul\n

    </string>

    <string name="orphanq">
        All they need is a little help, a little hope and someone who believes in them!
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

</resources>
